Well, I was wrong to be too confident.
When I went to the website after asking
it to bring it up, I got a page cannot
be displayed. I got a total fail.
Nothing was there. So, I went back to
the mayor and I said to the mayor,
there's nothing there. I didn't try and
debug it. Didn't diagnose it myself. I
just said, "Please just go ahead and fix
it. Sling your tasks. Get the polls
involved. Let's make this happen." And
bam, it did it all over again. Lots of
things happened. uh all of these six
pole cats, eight pole cats all started
up, things happened and now we're coming
back for the second time. And I'll
mention again that we should give it
some credit because it's really starting
from absolute nothing. The other times
we've had a build using the market data
foundation and the extra documentation
for market data. This time it just
started from the spec, the plan.md, and
that was it. So it's a total build from
absolute scratch. That's what it had to
do. Uh, and it did it all massively
parallel. So, it's very fast. By far the
fastest of any of the things that I've
done. And a couple of other things to
mention that you in the terminology. You
saw me struggling there a bit, but I I I
do now remember the thing called
refinery that was running was a special
uh agent, a special worker that is
responsible for doing the merge
requests, the MRS, and that's merging in
the work that all the others are doing.
So the reason that that was idle for a
long time is because it wasn't there
were no there were no MRS for it to
merge and then it would suddenly pick up
an MR when one of the pulcats was done
and that's why you'd see it like kick
into gear and the reason that there was
a red refinery there was because of that
other project I told you about that I'd
run before called finally so it had its
own refinery that was kind of dead uh
and that that's what was going on and
the process called witness is the thing
responsible for watching all of this and
notifying I think it notifies the mayor
uh if anything were to go wrong. So,
that's how it all hung together. And
now, without further ado, let's see if
we have a product. All right, here we
go. I told it to bring it up on port
802. Here we go. We do have a product.
We do have a product and it looks
remarkably similar to our other
products, which at the end of the day is
not super surprising because we spec
things out quite carefully in that in
that planning document and it was fairly
precise. And also, after all, it's
always clawed code. It's always Opus 4.6
that's building all of these. Um, but
it's interesting that we end up with
very similar results. So, here we have
something uh we've got over here on the
left. Um, and it's interesting this time
it says select a ticker from the watch
list. And maybe that's what I was meant
to do in the other one. If I think if I
click here, yeah, look at that. Then we
get to see uh the one that I just
clicked on appearing here in this chart.
And what happens now if I click here and
I say Apple quantity three and I click
buy then bang Apple appears in the
portfolio heat map over on the right. Uh
and I can also do uh Netflix and we will
buy for Netflix. Press buy and the heat
map has updated over here the portfolio.
We've got positions here. It's super
impressive. Particularly again, I mean,
we can't really call it zero shot this
time because it took it took an
iteration, didn't it? So, so it took two
iterations, but I didn't give it any
particular feedback. I didn't help it
troubleshoot. It figured all this out
for itself. And this whole thing is
running and it's alive. Wow. It's time
to try the LLM part. All right. So, over
here, I'll click in the chat. I'm going
to say hi there. And let's see what
happens. Takes a bit of time. Hello. How
can I help with your portfolio today?
Uh, I'm going to say, uh, please buy
three shares of JPM.
Let's see what happens. Drum roll,
please. Sure. I will place an order.
Bam. Look at that. JP Morgan appears
here. Nice and green. I like to see
that. And it's all uh updating
everywhere. The the AI chat works.
That's absolutely amazing. This is
great. This you see right here is the
result of running Gastown, building our
entire project, including the market
data simulator and the market data
interface, the whole thing built from
scratch and running and working. And so
to recap, if I haven't completely
confused you, we've been talking about
using orchestrators or patterns for
allowing us to manage multiple agents
working together, but with some level of
coordination between them to allow for
more predictable outcomes. And we've
really looked at three of them and we
could put them alongside each other in a
line from the most kind of controlled
and disciplined through to the most
crazy. The GSD, the get sh done is
perhaps despite the the radical sounding
name, the one that is most disciplined.
It is from the family of specd driven
designs. When there is a clear spec, it
uses markdown files very cautiously. It
goes through a period of plan of of
reviewing of execution and then
validating and then an audit at the end
of it. So it's this very reliable
disciplined process which lends itself
to bigger projects to human in the loop
and to being able to deliver measurable
predictable outcomes. Okay. So it's more
reliable, it's more slow. Then in the
middle we met clawed agent teams and it
was it's the experimental feature. Maybe
it's it's now more mature for you and
it's for sure it is faster. It took 5
hours with GSD. It took about half an
hour with Claude agent teams. And then
we ended on Gas Town. I just gave you a
preview of it. I told you you don't need
to do this yourself unless you
particularly want to go through the
experience that I went through when I
seemed a bit frazzled in places. But of
course, this this kind of thing is
emerging now. There are a few like it.
Guest town is the one that's quite hyped
at the moment, but there might be many
many more. And these are ones where
there is a sort of preset structure, but
it's it's it's ready for a lot of
concurrent work. It took about the same
time as Claude agent teams. I think in
total about half an hour but it did a
lot more because we gave it the market
data task as well. It built the whole
thing from scratch and it just all
worked second time but but just with me
telling it hey go and fix this and so
that was the most chaotic. It was the
fastest in terms of building the most in
the same amount of time and it was it
was pretty impressive if if a little bit
bewildering. And now GSD was is
something which can be applied to I
think all of the coding agents and gas
town is also something which Steve
points out a lot in the blog post is
something or in the GitHub read me
something that can be applied to the
different coding agents. It's not tied
to claw code even though he first built
it around it. Claude agent teams of
course is a feature built into claude
code but as it happens that very similar
feature similar agent features are built
into the others and in particular I I
took a look at codeex and codeex has
something that's also experimental built
into codeex and I wouldn't be doing my
job if I didn't quickly give you a sneak
peek of that. No surprise I'm sure
you're getting the idea that I most
favor the ones in the middle. I like
Claude agent teams a lot between these,
it was the one that gave me the
experience of of a lot of power without
feeling like I was completely out of
control. But I'm sure that if you spend
enough time with Gast Town, you get
really used to it. Anyway, let's go
check out Codeex sub agents. So, I'm not
actually going to run it cuz I I've
already run it and I think you've seen
enough of these now. I'm just going to
sort of show you show you the codecs and
and show you how you activate the
feature and then show you the results.
But I'm back in a normal terminal window
and I want to remind you of sprites.
Remember this. I can say sprite uh sorry
sprite.dev is the full name of it. I can
do sprite list to see all of the sprites
which I've got running. All of these
remote sandboxed environments that
fly.io is running for me. And I've got
one called finally worker, the same one.
And you can do sprite uh sprint sprite
minus s finally worker. That's how you
you say which one you're talking about.
and then console and that means I want
to like remote in I want this terminal
to become a terminal for that sprite and
that's what we're looking at right now.
So if I do an ls, I can see there's a
directory called finally in there. I can
go into finally. Now I'm in finally. And
this is in particular, if I do get
status, this repo is got uh it's on
branch codeex. I created this branch
called codeex. And when running codeex
inside your sprite, you just type
codeex. It's already installed, but you
do minus minus yolo. That is the
equivalent of dangerously skip
permissions uh for claude. They've got a
couple of them for yo for for codecs,
but d- yolo is one way to do it. And
we're now in codeex in yolo mode. And in
in codeex, you can do slash to bring up
a slash command menu just as with claw
code. And I went to /experimental,
which is where you get to toggle on and
off experimental features. And the one I
picked is called sub agents. Ask codeex
to spawn multiple agents to paralyze the
work and to win in efficiency. And so,
of course, I selected that. And then I
just said, "Hey, check out plan.md and
do this." That's what I did. It's not
the only thing I did cuz if I come out
of here, if I just do an ls, you'll also
notice that I renamed claude.md to
agents.md
because I remembered that codeex expects
agents.md, not claw.md. So that that
made it work. And I think I also told
it, let's have a look in scripts, uh,
cat start_mac.
Uh we can see what we've got right here.
Uh yeah, I I wanted it to come up on
port 803.
That's how it should run. Um so uh and I
believe that's that is now now running.
Let's do a docker ps to see if it's
running. Uh and this should tell us
whether or not docker is installed and
is running. And the idea is we expect it
to be running. It's not running. So I
will start it. Um I'll do scripts /
start.
And this is a Linux box, but Mac scripts
is the same. And now it should be coming
up and running. There we go. And it is
now running on port 803. So that is
built and running. It was built in
parallel. And I got to tell you, it was
super fast. It was faster than any of
them. I don't know if it just happened
to be having a good day. Uh but it was
really very quick. It it took uh I'd say
maybe 15 minutes end to end. So it was
the fastest as as these experiments go
of any of them. And we will see if we
can whatever zero shot it, see how it
is. if we try and bring it up. And of
course, it's running in my sprite on
port 803. And what I want to do is see
what's happening on my I want to be able
to bring it up on my computer on port
803. How's that going to work? I need to
like connect to the sprite out there in
the internet. But luckily, there's a
beautiful command I can do, which is
sprite minus s finally worker finally
dashworker. There's a command that is
called um proxy proxy. And then you do
the name of the port and that is going
to take port 803
on on Finally Worker and map it to my
local port. So I can just bring up a
browser, point it to 803 and see what's
going on on there. Okay, let's try